

## SHONTAN DANIEL AYODELE

GAME DEVELOPER | VISUAL ARTIST

### EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE GAMEPLAY PROGRAMMER • UPWORK, AFRICACOMICADE, TUNGA, THE GAME DEV COMMUNITY • JAN, 2020 – JULY 2021.

 Worked on multiple prototypes, created and cleaned up pc and mobile game projects for clients all over the game dev space.

JUNIOR GAME PROGRAMMER AND VISUAL ARTIST • PROJECT REDSHIELD, PINHEAD'S INTERACTIVE, SINGAPORE • SEP 2021 – DEC 2022.

- Designed and Programmed various aspects of game projects alongside team members that were assigned.
- Established and maintained a productive, professional working environment to promote the standing of the Company in the Gaming space.
- Implementation of Game Logics as well as the Functionalities of the Projects. From Player input all the way to UI interfacing and Game Management Systems.

#### 3D DEVELOPER • MICROLABACE • FEB 2019 - PRESENT

- Design, Characterization and Modelling of 3D assets for Virtual and Physical Environments.
- Proved successful working within tight deadlines and fast-paced atmosphere, especially on high end projects.
- Collaborated with team's members at Microlab achieve work on a virtual driving simulator.

# EDUCATION

Electrical, Electronics Engineering Technologies
OBAFEMI AWOLOWO UNIVERSITY, Ile-Ife, Osun State, Nigeria.

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Game Developer Familiar with C# and Developed multiple personal and professional Game Projects. An Online, Mobile and Windows Standalone Unity Game Developer Skilled in 3D landscape Construction and Design.

with 3+ years of experience in creating pc, mobile and web browser video games. High familiarity with Unity materials, Physics, Vector Mathematics, shaders, visual effects and 3D game assets.

### **SKILLS**

- Corporate visual standards
- Game rules understand-ding
- Strong graphic and visual sense
- Exceptional pre-production planning ability.
- Verγ Strong Coding and Design Sense.
- Good communication and relatability skills.
- Flexible to an ever change work Environment.







